Guide to the Edward Ginzton Papers SC0330
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1991-113
  - Leonard Cottrell's Comments on CONAES, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
  - CONAES, 1975-1979 (Box 10)
  - Outline of Final Report - December 31, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Interim Report Outline - March-July 1977 (Box 11)
  - Interim Report - (Box 11)
  - Chapters 1 -2 1977 (Box 11)
  - World Energy Outlook (Exxon Background) (Box 11)
  - Memos to CONAES from B.I. Spinrad (Box 11)
  - Comments by committee on draft 1, May 1, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Chapter 0, Summary 'The Role of Nuclear Energy (Box 11)
  - Chapter 1, Organization and Objectives of the study (Box 11)
  - Chapter 2, The Energy Problem (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -1-A To What extent can our Society moderate its patterns and trends of Energy growth? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -1-C How are Economic growth and quality of life related to Energy use in the U.S? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -1-D What is the relationship between our Society Structure Energy Policy Dec. - Making and our Patterns of Energy Supply and Use ? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -2-A, To What Extent can and Should U.S. draw on its fossil fuel resources until long-term Energy Technology can take over? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -2-B,How rapidly can and should we expand our use of Coal? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -2-C, What Role can and should Nuclear Energy plays in the U.S.Energy Supply System ? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, -2-D, What are ranges of possible mixes of Energy Supply delivery systems, that should provide our needs during transition to long-term sources ? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 3, Develop acceptable lg-term Energy sources (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 3 - A, How soon can Solar Energy make a substantial contribution to our Energy System ? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 3 - B, Should the U.S. Develop Breeder Reactors? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 3 - C, What is potential of Geothermal Energy as a long - term Energy source ? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 3-D, Is fusion likely to be a practical lg-term Energy source (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 4 - A, The Impact of U.S. Energy Police on Global Economic situation. (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 4 - B, Nuclear Power and Nuclear Proliferation. (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 4 - C, What are major Internatl. Environmental issues related to U.S. Energy Policy? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 3, 4- D, What is the relationship between U. S. and foreign Technology ? (Box 11)
  - Chapter 4, Analysis of Energy Scenarios (Box 11)
  - Chapter 5, Implications for Energy Policy and R&D, Thie White House remarks of the President to a joint of Congress. (Box 11)
  - Committee on Motor Vehicle Emissions (CMVE), 1964-1974 (Box 12-14)
  - Coordinating Committee for Air Quality Studies (CCAOS), 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - Conference on Air Quality and Automobile Emissions - May 5, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Semiannual Report by CMVE of the NAS to the Environmental Protection Agency, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Report by CMVE - February 15, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Report by CMVE - November 22, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 15)
  - Motor Vehicles, Air Pollution, and Health" - June 1962 (2 copies) (Box 15)
  - Background Material used by E. L. Ginzton for EPA Hearings - May 1973 (Box 15)
  - CMVE - NAS Hearings - January 26, 1972 (Box 15)
  - BUSINESS INTERNATIONAL ROUNDTABLE MEETINGS: (Box 16)
  - Rountable with the Government of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Business International Roundtable Nassau (Box 16)
  - Business International USSR Roundtable, 1971 (Box 16)
  - 1969 Conference Roster and Who' Who, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Financing Worldwide Corporate Expansion, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Business International Roundtable Jamaica, 1971 (Box 16)
  - The American Assembly, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Business International United Kingdom Roundtable, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Business International French Roundtable, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Business International French Government Roundtable, 1983 (Box 16)
  - BUSINESS INTERNATIONAL ROUNDTABLE MEETINGS (Box 17)
  - Business International Roundtable, United Nations (Box 17)
  - Business International Roundtable, Australian (Box 17)
  - Business International Roundtable, Japanese (Box 17)
  - Business International Roundtable, Bermuda (Box 17)
  - Business International Roundtable, European (Box 17)
  - China (Box 18)
  - Particle Accelerators and their applications, Beijing - China 1980 (Box 18)
  - China Briefing book - 1984 (Box 18)
  - China (Introduction to China) (Box 18)
  - 800,000,000 The Real China (Box 18)
  - Peking (Box 18)
  - The Chinese Academy of Sciences 1981 (Box 18)
  - Journal of Radiation REsearch and Radiation processing VOL 1, 2, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Chinese miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - China visit of Vice Premier (Box 18)
  - Trip Reports of E. L. Ginzton (Box 19)
  - E.L. Ginzton's visit to Japan and Taiwan (Box 19)
  - E.L. Ginzton's Taiwan trip 1977 (Box 19)
  - Pictures of Varian people in the Orient (Box 19)
  - 1966 - 67 Stanford University (Box 19)
  - Science in Hungary (Box 20)
  - Proceedings of the Colloquium on Microwave communication (Box 20)
  - U. S. and Soviet Trade Conference (Box 20)
  - Russian books (Box 20)
  - Hungarian Academy of Sciences (Box 20)
  - Guide to take Balaton (Box 20)
  - Leningrad guidebook (Box 20)
  - Budapest (Box 20)
  - Hungary, travel guide (Box 20)
  - Oral History Associates, Inc. (Box 21)
  - Stanford Oral History (Interviews with E. L. Ginzton) (Box 21)
  - Speeches of E. L. Ginzton (Box 21)
  - Historical material on the photographic slides on Russell and Sigurd Varian and Hansen's discorvery on the Klystron 1939. (Box 21)
  - Stanford Oral History tapes (Box 21)
  - ERDA (Box 22)
  - SERI (Solar Energy Research Institute - NAS) (Box 22)
  - NAS Solar Institute Study meeting - April 14 - 15 - 1975 (Box 22)
  - Radiation Therapy (Box 22)
  - Radar in World War II (Box 22)
  - Stanford - Hoover Institution (Box 22)
  - Radar (Box 22)
  - Electrophotography (Box 22)
  - MR Imaging and Spectroscopy (Box 22)
  - Genetic Targeting (Box 22)
  - SLAC (Box 22)
  - Physical and Mental Suffering of Experimental Animals (Box 22)
  - Comfortable quarters for Laboratory Animals (Box 22)
  - Alternative to animals use in Research, testing and education (Box 22)
  - The case for animal experimentation (Box 22)
  - Beyond the Laboratory door (Box 22)
  - Animal rights (Box 22)
  - Use of Laboratory animals in biomedical and behavior research (Box 22)
  - Varian tube policy in Europe (Box 22)
  - Booklet: Invention of the Klystron and founding of Varian Associates. (Box 23)
  - Booklet: Varian 25th Anniversary (Box 23)
  - Copy of Hansen's patent on a Resonant Cavity (Box 23)
  - Early correspondence regarding the Klystron (Box 23)
  - Varian's early History (Box 23)
  - Early Report on Varian Central Laboratory Research (Box 23)
  - Early letter from Hansen to Varian (Box 23)
  - Memo by Dorothy Varian, concerning Russell Varian (Box 23)
  - Memorandum by J. Arnold, regarding early NMR (Box 23)
  - Memorandum for publication by Russell Varian's Invention (Box 23)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning Invention of the Klystron, 1939 (Box 23)
  - Notes by William Hansen regarding the construction of his house, 1940 (Box 23)
  - Different photographs regarding early Varian (Box 23)
  - Letter from Russell to Sigurd, regarding information of Varian Associates (Box 23)
  - Early draft of Varian articles of incorporation; first meeting at Varian of Board of Directors (Box 23)
  - Oral History, Mercer: Martin Packard (Box 23)
  - The Varian Story, presented at the 1980 Pittsburgh conference by Martin Packard (Box 23)
  - Report of the proposed by Varian staff on proposed acquisition of Company X (Box 23)
  - Report by J. Osawa on 20 years of NEVA in Japan 1987 (Box 23)
  - Varian Magazine 50 anniversary of Klystron (Box 23)
  - Zerox copy of John and Agnews Varian (parents of Russell and Sigurd Varian) (Box 23)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1995-179
  - Abernathy, Susan (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anelva (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ansel Adams (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ansel Adams Photography Center (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Area 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biographies (1974-1991) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biographies (1959-1973) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bloch, Felix (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bd of Directors Desk File (1983-1990) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Governor (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budker, Prof (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Courtillot, Mano (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cron file current (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cron file Jan.-June 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cron file July-Dec 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cron file Jan.-June 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cron file July-Dec 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cron file Jan.-June 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cron file Jan.-Aug. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cron file Sept-Dec 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chodorow, Marvin (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cranston, Tunney etc. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - E.M.I (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eugenics (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Engineering Hall of Fame (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - English Klystron, CV-150 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ernst, Richard (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Expense Reports, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Exploratorium, The (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fellows Meetings, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fellows Meetings, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Finland (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Garner, John (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ginzton Scholarship (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hansen, Jim (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Housing-Hewlett-Packard (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hypothermia (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - I.E.E.E. 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - I.E.E.E. 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - I.E.E.E. Honorary Membership Com. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - India (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Instrument Group Task Force (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Leased Car Expenses (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Library (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Magmt. Meeting June 14-16 1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Malinowsky, Prof J (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Maps (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - McBride, William J. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Microwave Journal Article 7/78 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Microwaves (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - N.E.C. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Neva 1977–1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - N.M.R. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Britton Chance-N.M.R. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - N.M.R. Report 10/81 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Non financial Objectives/Varian (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Organ, Henry (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - One Hundred Dollar Idea, The (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Oral History by Sharon Mercer (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Osawa, Dr. J (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Peninsula Community Foundation (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Palo Alto City Council (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Panofsky Prize (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Passport Information (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Peninsula Community Foundation (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Perham Foundation-Electronics Museum (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Product Tree, The (Varian) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Radiotherapy for Arthritis (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Raychem (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Russia (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Russian Delegation, Visit of 10/23/86 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Reimbursements (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Schultz, Dr. Milton D Massachusetts Gen. Hospital (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - S.E.C. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Security Briefing Document (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sege, Tom, Cron File (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Service Awards Banquets (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Shields vs. Battaglia, et al (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Signature Authorizations (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Simpson, Gary (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subscriptions (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Systems Business (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - T & E Meeting (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Time Card Awareness Handbook (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Varian Alumni Group (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Varian Development Corp. (V.D.C) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Varian Foundation/Dorothy Varian (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Varian, Russell H. Portfolio IV Inventory (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - American Assembly (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences -- Western Center 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences -- Western Center 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences -- Western Center 1986–1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences -- Western Center Meeting March 18- 19, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences -- Western Center Meeting November 13–14, 1ª88 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences -- Western Center 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Engineering (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - William Miller's Nomination-N.A.E. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Science 1973-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Science--Annual Meetings (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Science--Bulgaria (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Science--Comm/Human rights (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Science--Nominations 1975–1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Science--Engineering, Beckman Center (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Science--Comm/Scientific & National Security 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Science--Correspondence 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Science--Nominations 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Science--Nominations 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Science--1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Science--N.R.C. (Animal Behavior) Trips: 1986, 1987, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - National Research Council-- 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Retirement Committee 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Committee Meeting 10/92 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Committee Meeting 8/91 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Committee Meeting 6/92 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Committee Correspondence 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Committee Meetings 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Committee Meetings 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Retirement Committee Agenda & Minutes (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Retirement Committee Correspondence 1988-91 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Retirement Committee Agenda & Minutes 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Retirement Committee Agenda & Minutes 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Retirement Committee Annual & Quarterly Reports (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Retirement Committee B.I.F. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Retirement Committee Charter (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Retirement Committee Correspondence 1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Retirement Committee Annual Reports to Directors (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Finance Commitee 8/92 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Committee--Legal Docs. & Adm Plan (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Committee J McDaniel's Meetings (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Committee Outside Member (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Committee Portfolio Insurance (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Board Meeting 2/93 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm T. E. Everhart (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm Ira Hall (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm J. M. Lillie (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm G. A. Maneatis (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm W. E. Massey (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm J. E. McDonald (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors--Adv Dir -D. E. Mundell (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors--Nomin Comm J. E. Robson (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda 1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors--Memoranda 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors Meeting- 5/92 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Meeting- 2/92 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Nomin Com - Agenda/Minutes-1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors O&C Mtgs 8/89 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Corresp. 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors Affiliations Prev Bd Mem (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Advis Directors (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Annual Agenda (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Audit Committee (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Basic Corp Objec (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Birth Dates (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors Chairmanship Authority (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors Committee Assignments (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors Compensation (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors Compos & Gen Policies (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors Spec Com Mts/ Continental Investigation (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors Deferred Compensation (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors Desk File 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors Divestment Policy (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors Executive Comm 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors Finance Committee 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors - Future Meetings (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors - Dr. Gibbon's Invention (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors - Incentive Compensation Committee (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors - Indemnity Agreement (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors - Korn Ferry (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors - Leadership/Mgmt of Co (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors - LW Lehr (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors - AA McNaughton (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors - Trip Tokyo 4/89 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors - Magazines/Clippings (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors - Minutes 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors - Bd Members 1948-1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors - Booklet "The New Director (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors - 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Comm, Biog Inf 1988-90 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Comm, Corresp. 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors - Memoranda 1983-1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors - Agenda & Minutes 1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1986 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Com Agenda & Minutes 1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors - Biographical Inf 1983 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors - Agenda/Minutes 1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors - Agenda/Minutes 1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors - Agenda/Minutes 1978-80 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors - Biographical Inf 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors - Biographical Inf 1982 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors - Biographical Inf 1981 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Comm Corresp. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors - Nomin Comm Corresp. 1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Contributions Committee (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Cron File July-Dec 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cron File Jan.-June 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cron File July-Dec 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cron File Jan.-June 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gen Operations Comm - 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gen Operations Comm - 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Peninsula Housing Coal. - July-Dec 88 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Board Dinner - 12/15/88 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Mgmt Mtgs - 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mgmt Mtgs - 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Mgmt Mtgs - 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Mid-Peninsula Housing Coal. - 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Mid-Peninsula Housing Coal. - July-Dec 90 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Mid-Peninsula Housing Coal. - Jan.-Jun 90 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Mid-Peninsula Housing Coal. - Jul-Dec 89 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mid Peninsula Housing Coal. - Jan.-Jun 88 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University - SLAC (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University - SLAC: Corresp. 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - SLAC: Corresp. 1984-1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - SLAC: Corresp. 1982-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University - SLAC: Corresp. 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University - SLAC: Corresp. 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University - SLAC: Corresp. 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bd of Trustees - General 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University - Centennial Campaign (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University - Chemistry Dept. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - Contributions (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - Engineering School (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University - Engineering School Advisory Council (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University - Fellows Program (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University - Friends of Radiology (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University - Bd of Trustees - General 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University - Housing (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University - Major Gifts Committee (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University - Med Cr Fundraising Program (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University - White Knight (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Alphabetical: A-Z (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - SSRL: 1985-1990 (Stanford Synchrotron Radiation Laboratory - All Related Files) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Varian Video Report (Empowerment Comes to Life) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Govt Affairs Dept. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Communications (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Finance Division (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Committee FIF (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Committee - Fund Performance (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Retirement GICs (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Retirement Committee - Financial Schedules (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Retirement Committee - Correspondence 1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Retirement Committee - Report to Bd/Directors (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Retirement Committee - Coopers & Lybrand (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - International Operations (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Ralph Kane (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Patent Dept. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Martin Packard (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Silicon Valley Technology CR (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Varian Associates, Bylaws, 1948 - 1972 (Box 17, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, April 26, 1948 - June, 6, 1957 (Box 17, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, June 24, 1957 - December 1961 (Box 18, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, January 1962 - September 1966 (Box 19, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, October 1966 - February 1971 (Box 20, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, May 1971 - November 1976 (Box 21, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, February 1977 - November 1981 (Box 22, Folder Vols)
  - Varian Associates, Board of Directors and Share Holders, Minutes, March 20, 1981 - February 25, 1983 (Box 23, Folder Vols)
- Photographs, Accession ARCH-1996-059 (Box 1)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1998-231
  - Varian Foundation- Castle Rock St. Park Completion Plan, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - V.A.- Task Force on Stockholders' Rights, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - V.A.- Retirement Committee (Box 1, Folder 3)